For those who are asking what the
insurance is that is sometimes
mentioned in my videos, this is it
guys, the
beauty of it guys is that
your monthly premium from day one until
you finish your insurance payment is the
same price as what you would pay monthly
and there are no hidden charges but what
I chose guys is an annual payment so
I don't have to think about anything for a whole year So
I can save up and invest
my payment in my insurance policy
before the end of the year what is
covered by it and why did I take sun fit and
well, watch this
Why is sun fit and well
my favorite insurance product
of sunlife if you haven't watched my
previous video yet a few days back I
shared the different traditional
insurance plans of Sun Life so you can
check it out if you want to be
familiarized somehow down with those that are in
sunlife Actually this is also
my first insurance plan with sun life I
got it 5 years ago Why is this
my favorite whether I am an Agent or
not this is really the one I would choose
whether as my first  plan or as a
subsequent insurance because
I believe that health insurance coverage is so important
whatever life stage you are in
whether you are married or not single
or not breadwinner or not especially
in our country that
public health care is not really that good by
the way This is not to be confused with
HMO or medical insurance because on
fit and well it's really concerned with
critical illness coverage HMO
medical insurance is more concerned with the
checkup in the lab during confinement Even
if it's not a critical illness that happened
SAO Anyway This is it Why is this
my favorite first is you only pay
for 10 15 or 20 years meaning
you only pay for a limited time then
your payment has not increased But
you are covered until age 100 So that's virtually
for life because in fact in other
insurance plans the others there
your premium increases as you age especially
when you have critical illness coverage
also others you pay for a lifetime
or for a very long period of time also
here because even when you don't get sick
no so no  If you claim critical
illness it will just turn into life
insurance or death benefit also
my favorite part is Once I am
done paying so in my case I I chose the
15 years to pay plan On the 15th year
I will be eligible to receive a special
paid up bonus as a reward because
I am done paying also I'll be getting annual
dividends 1 year later and those
dividends that I will give to me
as long as the policy is enforced and as
long as Sun Life is earning now if I
live healthy long enough there's even a
possibility that because of the dividends
and the bonus when I save those it will
almost be
realized for asset protection because
Just in case I get sick and
have a big hospital bill the
money won't be moved or sold I hope there is money So that
guys is my Purpose why I
bought life and health insurance and
Just in case I say goodbye to the world
I have a million money to leave
for my future family because
guys we are not yet blessed  God gave me a
partner in life so the benefit I will give you
now is my mom I
regret guys that I didn't immediately
get life and health insurance when
I was just starting to become an OFW
who was still below 30
because the monthly premium is cheaper when
you are below 30 because guys every
birthday you pay more
for your insurance Especially when
you go over 30 so Is it
really important to have life and
health insurance? Watch this
video by uncle
singkitan there is a question here if
insurance is really important
the answer is Absolutely Yes You know
everything now that is important is in-in
ah perfect example of that is the car is the
car
drunk amage Likewise life is also like that
life is more
important a car if the
car is an inanimate object
really protected how much more than
life Good car If it crashes it
can be repaired but a person's life
Like for example if it crashes it can't be
replaced So if you ask me
insurance is really important Yes take note
guys if you want to get
life and health insurance and  When someone
offers you and tells you that they
are asking you for a fee and that you can
fill up or fill out a life and
health insurance policy even if
you are in another country, you guys should be surprised
because an applicant can only fill out life
and health insurance
when you return to the Philippines for
your vacation. It is not possible while
you are in another country because it is not valid.
So to avoid being scammed and if
you want to get your life and health
insurance when you return to the
Philippines for your vacation,
just contact my kind and
attentive financial advisor because
guys, I got my life and
health insurance from him. So when I went on vacation
to the Philippines, I signed up there
and when I came back to this other country,
he sent it to me here in Dubai
and it arrived very quickly. So guys,
I will put his contact number
and also his Facebook page in the
description of this video so you can find it
and so you can contact him so that
you can also get your life and
health insurance so that
your future is secure.